Hello and welcome back. So, now in this video what we want to do is whenever we kill a
zombie we want the zombie to instantiate a health power-up or a ammo power-up. So,
in order to do that, you will have to open up the zombie prefabs. Okay, select all of them.
Here they are, let's lock it. Okay, so all of these zombies are locked. Let's click on it
component and make sure that you are this Arto instantiate component to it and then in the
prefab to instantiate. Let's go ahead and add the prefab so it sends a 12% controller prefab's
game, interactable. There it is. So, try and drop the health power and then the ammo. Okay,
when you try and drop that, then open up to do health of all of these zombies and click on this
on that event and you need to add that. Right, but let me first of all, take the record and now
let's do it one by one for each zombie. Okay, so on this zombie, the Arto instantiate is added
now in the health. Let's add on that event. Try and drop this Arto instantiate right there
and then Arto instantiate instantiate prefab. All right, you're going to do the same for the next
zombie. Try and drop that and select the instantiate prefab. Okay, let's do it right here as well.
Then for this zombie as well. And then for the final one right here.
All right, now whenever a zombie is skilled at the instantiate, either health power or a
poor ammo power-up, but also select all of these zombies and make sure that you remove this.
Start instantiate on a way. Okay, remove that. That is all you have to do.